Guide to the David C. Evans audio-visual collection 1972-1987
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- Corporate overview, 1984 May; Audiocassette (Cassette 8)
  A ten minute commercial overview of Evans & Sutherland, "a Salt Lake City company located adjacent to the University of Utah that makes computer graphics systems for research, design, entertainment, and training." The narration includes Evans & Sutherland history from 1968 to current times, descriptions of their products and the people who use them, and their work ethic.